

## Praramvik Das

### Contact

### **Address**

Chandmari Colony Nizarapar, House No-9. Guwahati, Assam -781003

# **Phone** 8095548756

### **Email**

praramvikdas2018@gmail.com

### Additional Skills

Team Work
Taking Initiative
Ability to Work Under Pressure
Self-motivation
Decision Making
Time management
Proficient in Microsoft Office
Excellent written and
Verbal communication skill
Creative Thinking
Responsible
Accuracy
Confidence
Creative

• PROFESSIONAL SKILLS -

## Summary

I am Praramvik Das and I belong from Guwahati, Assam. I have come to know about the job opening in your organization from sources and wish to appear for an interview on this. I have a total experience of 5+ years in various fields which includes Customer Support, Sales, Marketing, Finance in the US Mortgage and US Voice Process.

I understand that working for your organization requires a candidate who is team oriented and is able to deal with people in various departments. I am confident and I possess these skills, which will help me to perform the job efficiently and effectively.

My goal is to transit my enthusiasm, creativity and experience into a position, where I continue to provide the strategic and tactical leadership critical to retaining valued customers of an organization. I am certain that my presence in your team will prove to be beneficial to your organization. As such, I would welcome an opportunity to speak with you to evaluate your needs and share my ideas.

## Work Experience

**APRIL 2015 TO MAY 2016** 

## LITTLE INTERNET PVT LTD, BANGALORE

• JOB TITLE: CUSTOMER SUPPORT SERVICE, VOICE PROCESS (INBOUND & OUTBOUND), SALES In this organization, I was working as a CSE. My role was to attend the calls from customers and resolve the queries at an early basis such as initiating refunds, validating coupon codes, troubleshooting etc. And along with this we are supposed to make sales on the desired product the customer is looking for or suggesting them the right choice.

### • Strengths:

Working calmly in the most pressurized situation and listening to the customer issues I was precisely resolving them.

MAY 2016 TO AUGUST 2017

### VISIONET SYSTEMS PVT LTD, BANGALORE

• JOB TITLE: US MORTGAGE PROCESS, VOICE (INBOUND & OUTBOUND)

In this organization, I was working as a Senior Associate in the Mortgage process. My role was to call the County Office and get the update on the mortgage documents from the County Officer regarding the Recording Numbers of the documents and the same we use to update to our clients. I was doing Submission on E-Record, Workflow, Order Entry and Bulk Uploads of documents.

### • Strengths:

Completing the given work before deadlines & Resolving Client Escalations in a proper manner.

## DIGITAL MARKETING, DANCE CHOREOGRAPHER

Reference: Sharukh Ahmed HR Assistant Manager

#### NOVEMBER 2017 TO DECEMBER 2019

### FIRSTSOURCE SOLUTIONS PVT LTD, BANGALORE

• JOB TITLE: PULTE MORTGAGE PROCESS, US
In this organization, I was working as a Senior Associate in the Pulte
Mortgage Process, US. My role was to check all the Mortgage
documents which was sent by the Loan Processor to recheck and
verify the documents. Once the documents are verified it goes for
Underwriting. We were also need to do multiple task in the CRM
according to the desired documents and making sure to clear the
complete pipe line on the given TAT.

### • Strengths:

Completing the given work before deadlines with proper quality measures and making the business grow with teamwork.

Reference Lohit (Assistant Manager) Vinoth (Team Leader)

DECEMBER 2019 TO JANUARY 2021

### **WECARE HOLIDAYS PVT LTD, SIKKIM**

• JOB TITLE: DIGITAL MARKETING

In this organization, I was doing Digital Marketing as a freelancer for their Website. My role was to do SEO on both On page and Off page of their website and handling all the Social Media platforms for marketing and generating leads.

• Strengths: SEO, Google Ads, Facebook Campaigns, Lead Generations, etc.

### Education

### **BLUE PINE SCHOOL, GUWAHATI**

CLASS 10 PASS OUT

### **B.BOROOAH COLLEGE, GUWAHATI**

• STREAM - COMMERCE (XI & XII)

### **GUWAHATI COMMERCE COLLEGE, GUWAHATI**

• BACHELOR OF COMMERCE

### Languages

ENGLISH — FLUENT

HINDI — FLUENT

KANNADA — MILD

ASSAMESE — FLUENT

## Personal Details

Fathers Name: Bipul Das

Address: Chandmari Colony, Nizarapar. Guwahati, Assam-781003

Phone: 8095548756 DoB: 18/06/1994 Gender: Male Nationality: Indian Marital Status: Single

Hobbies: Dancing, Singing, Travelling, Learning New Skills, etc.